well I was hoping you
uh I was hoping you would you would miss
that question but of course uh I get
asked that question at least once a day
um well I the only way to explain it is
uh my parents had very high hopes I I
was named after my uncle uh who was a
famous doctor back in Gambia and uh and
uh they they they wanted they wanted me
to become just like him and so uh they
named me Dr caram casama after my
uncle awesome and uh did you um you're
you're I guess you're not getting into
the medical field anytime soon uh but
did you have hopes that one day that you
would have been a
doctor well you you should never say
never I mean I have one degree but uh
who knows maybe one day I'll I'll uh go
back for a second but but as of right
now that's not my focus for sure for
sure
hi there my name is Ryan Perez owner of
the hustle Zone thank you Susan for
letting me know that I have no sound uh
so this has been a long time since I've
been uh doing the uh it's been a couple
of months since I've actually done an
official hustle Zone show and um I'm
super excited for uh tonight's guest uh
but before I go there I I really want to
thank all the people that have supported
this uh entrepreneur movement that we've
kind of created with the hustle Zone you
know we've had people buying the sweater
I don't know if you guys can see that so
uh we've had people buying the t-shirts
and the tank tops um so I really
appreciate that so you want to make sure
um that you check out get that tea so
it's so like Philip Woods I'm just
telling you you know that name is really
hard to it's like a tongue twister get.
datat T and it's geyen doyen t
tee.com uh so um all of my followers and
supporters if you guys have the link can
you kindly post that in the description
um thank you so much uh we are now
taking interview like we are opening up
the calendar again for people to um to
to get interviewed on the hustle zone so
make sure that you um you know message
me and I'll send you the link uh the
calendar link uh to do so um so the
other thing too is that we got how many
writers I think we're at 12 um 12
writers one editor uh one photographer
for the the online magazine so you guys
are really pulling through um people are
getting mad at me yesterday because I
have I haven't been
answering their their messages so folks
just let you know I run a business and
uh and then on top of that I run the
hustle zone so it's really hard for me
to get to everybody but like I'm getting
messages like all day and all night long
you would think I'm liono Richie right
like I just so many messages so uh thank
you guys so much for for for messaging I
will get back to you as soon as possible
uh but thank you guys again for your
support the the hustle Zone magazine we
don't have a launch date yet because we
got to get the content in but um uh uh
once we get that in uh we'll let you
know an official launch date so thank
you guys so much uh the other thing too
is yesterday's show was amazing we had
um uh we started a pilot show called the
great debate where we were talking about
um you know whether
MLM is a legitimate business or not
right so we got some very interesting
conversations so we're going to do that
great debate again um and we're going to
talk about hi Scott thank you for liking
uh we're going to talk about um
prenups should should you or should you
not get a prenup if you're an
entrepreneur I mean these are questions
that you know they're very uh like I
don't know they're really controversial
questions but these are these are
questions that a lot of people ask and a
lot of people argue over so we want to
hear your we want to hear your your um
your point of view uh on that uh
tomorrow so make sure you guys tune in
for that so uh so I'll let you I'm we're
going to get to the next part so the
reason why I've been away for so long
and I've been telling you that I've been
working on a project that um has been
you know I've been working night and day
and this project and in addition to
other projects that I've been working on
but this has been the
my life for the last two
months and um and and and be and I love
the project so much because it does such
a great thing uh and we're going to get
into that in a second but I I'm going to
blame my guest for the reason why I've
been away from from you all I'm going to
blame
him because he has me working working
hard uh but he is a young entrepreneur
25 years
old okay let let that sink in let that
sink in 25 years old and you know he
started a
international
company you know so he's flying all over
the world he has people flying all over
the world you know to bring this this
this project that he's working on into
fruition and you know I had the pleasure
in working on the website and actually
building the website and you know it is
it's the only website of its kind in
Canada okay and what he's doing now I
don't know if a lot of you because I
know a lot of entrepreneurs like oh man
school I don't like school but you know
um I we all know someone that is in
school um youve probably went to school
you probably went for you know took
business management or what have you um
and if you could remember filling out
your
application some of you you probably
filled your application out by hand like
actually filled out a piece of
paper um others have went onto a website
and filled out an application and
realized that it was just not really
easy to use and these websites are
really hard to use
um and then you're just applying to just
one one
website you're not applying to multiple
the other issue is is that
um you have to pay to to to apply at
some of these schools schools you have
to play and and then Min and then
miny and um so that's also an
issue um my guest today has built a
website um and and and we've partnered
up and I've helped build this website
that eliminates all those
issues you have an easy form to fill out
and all you have to do is apply
once and I think that's amazing I think
that's awesome you apply once you get
seen by multiple
universities no admin
fees and and Canada the place where I'm
from being able to study in Canada
Canada is a wonderful place to
live and
Doc and his name is Doctor by the way
and we're going to get to that once I
get him on uh but his his name is Doctor
and he is a brilliant man and you know
very ambitious he's a he's a he's a risk
taker he put this website together and
um so I'm going to bring him in in a few
seconds but you know he he he also was a
student here in Canada uh he went to the
University of Calgary uh he was uh star
football player in uh uh for the the
University of Calgary's dinos um you
know so he he and you know he's been in
the newspap paper I mean I've come
across you know I before I met him I I
came across uh what he's done um in the
past so I mean you know a lot of people
know who he is and I I I I'm going to
stop the rambling and I'm going to get
him on right now so everyone I want you
guys to say hello to Mr doc casama how
are you
doing hi Ryan I'm doing well thank you
thanks for having me on the show uh um
what did you think about the long-
winded
introduction well I was I was I was
listening to you and and uh it's it's
hard it's it's it's not easy to always
hear someone else talk about you but you
did a great job so I appreciate that
well thank you I mean you know
um not only are you like I'm not
bringing you on because you're my client
I'm bringing you on because you are you
know a phenomenal man you know you're a
a phenomenal person that has built a
great website that's going to pretty
much revolutionize the way that people
do um way that people apply in Canada
for universities so are you aware of how
you know what what what you're doing
here
well it's it's been a long process Ryan
um um I'm I'm very thankful for for
having this
opportunity I think uh I've been blessed
uh uh with this idea but most
importantly the people that are
supporting this idea that are partnered
uh with this business I think that
speaks more volume than the idea itself
and so I'm I'm very excited for what
this can do for students but also for
for the country of Canada so doc you
you're uh let's let's talk about the
first um and and just so that everyone
knows uh what is the hustle Zone The
Hustle Zone we capture the spirit of the
entrepreneur we are trying to establish
entrepreneurialism as a culture as a way
of life as a way of being uh the hustle
Zone uh a lot of people think that being
an entrepreneur is a myth that you know
that you're almost like a ghost and if
you're really super successful it's
because you had it by luck or because
you had money or what have you but a lot
of people don't realize that being an
entrepreneur
uh takes a lot of good habits you know
and and we have just different habits so
um I just want to start that off I know
I have to uh start that off every show
that I do but you know I really want
people to understand that we're trying
to capture the spirit of the
entrepreneur you know we want to know
what what makes the entrepreneur tick uh
but the first question before I ask the
major question that I normally ask at
every hustle Zone uh Doc is
um your your parents named you doctor
so and I'm sure because they wanted you
to be a doctor so can you explain about
that a little bit well I was hoping you
uh I was hoping you would you would miss
that question but of course uh I get
asked that question at least once a day
um well I the only way to explain it is
uh my parents had very high hopes I I
was named after my uncle uh was a famous
doctor back in Gambia and uh and uh they
they they wanted they wanted me to
become just like him and so uh they
named me Dr caram casama after my
uncle awesome and uh did you um you're
you're I guess you're not getting into
the medical field anytime soon uh but
did you have hopes that one day that you
would have been a
doctor well you you should never say
never I mean I have one degree but uh
who knows maybe one day I'll I'll uh go
back for a second but but as of right
now that's not my focus for sure for
sure um so doc when uh people would get
mad at me if I didn't ask this question
so I'm going to ask um ask the famous
question doc tell us your story so tell
us how it all happened how all began and
start from the very beginning we have
all
day start from the beginning and folks
I'll just tell you he's like yeah it's
going to be about 15 20 minutes I'm like
uh probably not not with the hustles on
so we we're going to you know we we have
all day to to hear about your story but
you know you can give us whatever you
like but just let us know how it all how
it all happened how did you become an
entrepreneur and you know and even tell
us about your your football
career well hey that's great story I
I'll give you guys the short version um
I was born in Gambia and and moved to
Sweden at a young age um for some reason
out of our own the sports that you can
play in Sweden in Sweden um you know the
most popular sport is soccer and hockey
but I decided to play American football
and so uh anyways uh it's something that
I was good at immediately and I had a
dream at a very young age to to to earn
a scholarship and and uh go overseas and
play football in North America so I work
very hard for that goal and uh
eventually earned a scholarship at the
University of Calgary and and came
here uh to pursue football and an
education and so um so as I came here
that's that's when I really started
growing so I finished my degree at the
University of Calgary uh uh um um you
know took football as far as I could uh
try out with the Green bayy Packers and
uh and eventually decided to go into
business that's my real passion and so
uh that's that's that's why I'm still in
Canada because it's been so good to me
and uh Calgary is my home right now
that's awesome uh so
doc did you have when you first CU I
guess you you immigrated here from uh or
uh you immigrated here from from Sweden
so that you could pursue your education
right uh and with the tensions of
there's a lot of tension in terms of
just you know flying into a new country
where you have to learn new customs and
things of that nature like what was your
experience um you know first landing
into
Canada well I've been very blessed you
know I've I've lived in three different
continents and so uh I I like I said I I
grew up in West Africa I I lived in
Sweden in Europe and then I moved to
North America so i' I've lived in
different places and so um but moving to
Canada I was definitely not ready for
the weather the winters um that's that's
the number one thing but uh I got used
to it and um and Canada has been a
blessing to me and and there's a reason
why I'm still here but I've never been
in a place where people are more welcome
uh people
are um you know they're helpful but also
it's a very Multicultural place so no
matter what no matter where you come
from you know you feel at home here
right and I I mean you know being a
Canadian I I you know I I feel like
especially with what's going on um in
the world right now I mean immigration
is a really hot topic and being Canadian
um and growing up here you know there
are some benefits there's definitely
some we you know I I feel like our
society you know we have a lot of um
inclusion like I mean like people just
feel like they're together right
and
I when I look at you know the the news
right now we we see what's happening
with Donald Trump um and IM you know
with with the Syrian refugees Etc I mean
you know tensions are very high so I
mean that's why you know you started
this this company to bring people to
Canada because it it it is a wonderful
place um and and with just even with
Justin Trudeau right now saying hey you
know you know we welcome everyone with
open arms I think that's amazing so can
you expound on you know how how do you
feel with the the the turmoil that's
happening in the international media in
terms of you know um
immigration well uh I'm not really a
politician but but uh I can only speak
from experience and uh and uh coming to
Canada uh was the best decision that I
made in my life and and for several
reasons but um I believe that you know
um I could live anywhere in the world
right now whether it go back to Sweden
Europe or you know move to a different
country but Canada has been so good to
me there's so many opportunities here
and the reason why started this business
is because I came here as an
international student and the experience
was so good that uh I decided to stay
and so uh you know I know right now the
government of Canada has open the door
for international
students uh to come and get an education
and and as well as uh change their lives
you know that's what happened to me so
Canada really changed my life and and I
I everywhere I go where where whether I
go back to Sweden or whether I go to you
know Asia or Africa I always found
myself bragging about Canada so uh I you
know the experience I had with coming
here I want to give that same experience
to to to Young you know women and men
that that that are looking for an
opportunity that are looking to you know
get educated and achieve their dreams so
tell me uh let's uh dial it back a
little bit tell me a little bit about um
entrepreneurialism what does
entrepreneurialism mean to
you what does it mean to me I think it
means to to follow your passion and do
it very well you know I think a lot of
people um settle for less than what they
want I think
entrepreneurship is knowing what you're
passionate about and and uh and uh doing
that to the best of your
ability and if you can earn an income
from it even better right and what what
got you into entrepreneurialism like
what was the thing that really sparked
your your you know your passion and and
and the fact that you want to follow
your passion what was the thing that
really motivated you to get to this
place huh you know I like I said my
whole life I grew up playing sports I
was very good at football but when I
came to Canada that's that's what really
um that's when I got exposed to to
entrepreneurship and business and so in
my second year second year of University
or third year uh I was introduced to
some mentors uh that were entrepreneurs
and and and uh they took me under their
wing as I was in
university and and they taught me about
business they taught me about how you
know life is really short so
we don't have
time uh uh uh pursuing things other than
our passions and so uh they helped me uh
get the mindset and grow myself really
and gave me some really good books that
changed my life forever and are one of
those books thinking Grow Rich
absolutely that's one of them and
there's there's many more and what what
other books have you
read um you know um books by by uh by
John Maxwell good good leaders good
leaders ask great questions um there's
books by Napoleon
Hill um you know three feet from gold
there's there's um another book called
um what is it what's his name
um um you know the richest man in
Babylon there's there's many books that
have changed my life life and and and
many different authors wow you know what
book I read I read um I did read I
believe it's the richest man in Babylon
and like and
and I don't know if this the same is it
about
Solomon is that book about
Solomon um yes it's about a rich not
Solomon I think it's about a a a a very
wise and wealthy person but I don't
think it's a
yeah I read a book um that was kind of
on the similar um it was a someone had
given it to me uh a a friend um and it
was about King Solomon and how you know
he never really prayed for wealth right
he just prayed for wisdom and and
understanding and and and whatnot I mean
I'm not I personally am not religious
but I still took the book you know at
what it was I mean you know and I think
as an entrepreneur work constantly just
like how you just mention all these
books you're constantly learning and
you're wanting to you know learn from
the great you can't just do this on your
own you you know you can't just you know
some people are lucky but you know not
not everyone I I there's a there's a
quote by Will Smith actually it says Uh
there's there's two ways to reach your
goals very fast there's two ways to
reach it one is to go out and run
because you're working your mind and and
and and every time I go out and
run you know my mind tells me to stop
but when you keep going you push through
and and and secondly there is to read
books because if you want to get from
point A to point B and there's someone
that's already done it and they've
written it in a book you know that's
your fastest way of getting there by
reading the
book speaking of which um there's a I
think there's a there is a just a shift
in in terms of education and in people's
attitudes towards education uh as an
entrepreneur there there are people out
there that are kind of discount they're
discounting education they're saying
well you don't have to have an education
you don't have to read to be a
successful entrepreneur and I've heard
that a few times but I've heard a lot of
people including Robert kosaki um and a
few other um business people that say
that education um you know doesn't it
doesn't make you successful and what
what is your perspective on
that my perspective is
uh I think you have to know what you
want and and I think a lot of people go
into
education uh not knowing what they want
but I think uh if you go into
education you want to go in there
knowing
uh knowing knowing what you want out of
the education right and so I went into
education you know to be honest not
necessarily knowing what I wanted but
eventually I ended up getting a a
communications degree because I enjoy uh
um you know I enjoy public speaking and
I enjoy uh impacting people but um I
think you know knowledge is only
powerful if you use it and so going into
education uh I think I think the key is
going in there knowing what you want out
of it and that way you will get much
more out of it than just going in there
and and uh not having a clue what you
want to do with it right you know it's
almost like you shouldn't go you know if
you if you're not um and you know
because you'd have to get into debt Etc
you shouldn't go and waste up your time
trying to figure things out you should
kind of have a clear Direction on on
where like I mean I'm not saying you
should go I mean I'll take that back I I
think that you can learn as much and I
mean I didn't I didn't go through the
education um path but I was constantly
reading textbooks and and whatnot
because there's always there's just so
much knowledge but I think you're right
you you do have to have a purpose and do
you think that people are do people know
their purpose you know especially
because I mean you're 25 years old like
are a lot of young people really
thinking about their purpose in
life I I don't think so a lot of people
uh my age or younger they wouldn't know
that and and and that's okay you know I
think it takes time and experience to
know that uh but for me going into
education definitely helped me um help
me to understand what I want out of life
so I'm I'm so thankful for for for the
degree that I have and the opportunity
to to get educated I mean I I I've been
to I've traveled around around the world
and I've seen you know I've seen rich
neighborhoods and poor neighborhoods and
and to be honest I think I believe truly
that getting educated that education is
is an
opportunity and and that gives people
hope you know and and I think education
is the key to to a lot of solutions
right and and I've seen I've seen it
when when I you know travel to Africa or
Asia
where people are not educated all the
time and it's um it's it's it's it's not
always easy but I think um you know
giving someone money or giving someone
food they will always come back for more
but when you educate someone uh then
they have the knowledge and the hope to
get things done on their own right right
now uh speaking of Education let's talk
about education Solutions Canada so this
is a you know revolutionary website um
uh I believe the first in
Canada uh to you know to recruit um
students from all over the world
including Canada recruit students or I
don't know if it's a recruiting uh
website but more so it's a place where
um students can go fill out an
application and be seen by multiple
people so can you expound upon that and
let everyone know about your
company yeah education Solutions Canada
um started as I said uh uh knowing what
how great uh Canada treating me and so I
want to give that same opportunity to
kids around the world as well as
Canadian kids so we believe that that we
have a solution to to to some of the uh
some of the ways Education Works in
Canada and so uh what it is it's a
platform that we've built that any
student whether Canadian or
International can apply from anywhere in
the world and they create a profile and
then we give access to universities and
colleges to view your profile so we kept
you know the biggest thing is is is is
we want to keep the student in mind and
uh we want to create a win-win situation
for the student as well as the
university institutions for the student
we're saying hey instead of you applying
to you know 10 or 20 different you know
10 or five different universities and
paying multiple application fees you
know the students are big asset to the
universities so I believe that uh uh the
students should apply for free and then
we give access to multiple universities
to look at the student profile which
gives the student a much a much higher
uh a chance of getting accepted right so
uh so and and and of course candidate is
the I think uh the best country to live
in and and and to get your education and
so uh that's why we that's why we
started this thing and uh and and it's
not just you I mean you you you you run
a
corporation and uh so you have other
teammates that have helped you build
this initiative uh you can you tell us a
little bit about them right I I say to
me you know uh educ Solutions Canada the
the the people that are involved in it
the the three direct directors
myself uh Barbara Cox and sandre wig uh
you know that speaks more
volume uh uh to me than than anything
else you know I I like to brag about my
team there's a lot more people involved
but uh um when I created this thing I
knew that uh in order to be successful
in in any Venture you need a really
strong team so we have a really diverse
team of uh of uh myself and and our vice
president who's uh Barbara Cox who's
who's very experienced in in the
business world and comes from a
different background than me and then we
have a Sandra wig who uh who's worked
with these universities for years and
years and and so she understands uh the
struggles that that National students as
well as International students go go
through so we have a team of uh diverse
backgrounds but together uh uh we make a
very strong team right and so on uh um
and then upon building the website um
did you what were like before you built
the
website what what was going in your mind
you know and did you think that you were
were you were going to be able to
achieve what you've built
now well I
um you know one thing I've learned is is
is you know you take an idea from your
head and you try to implement it uh uh
one thing I've learned it's a lot more
work than you expected and uh uh you
know building this website has been a a
tremendous experience and I feel like we
we overachieved our goals in terms of
building the website and and thanks to
you and and what you've done Ryan but uh
we're very happy with the product and
and uh we're constantly going to have to
improve this because we're dealing with
students and and we are putting the
students first you know we want to we
want to make this thing as userfriendly
as possible for the students because a
lot of students uh uh the feedback we've
get we've been we've got is that you
know going on to these different
University sites and and trying to apply
for an application it's it's very very
it's very hard and it's very time
consuming and it's very um how do you
explain it it's it's not an easy thing
to to to Gras right away right so what
we've done is we've built an easier way
for any student to apply from anywhere
in the world and be seen by multiple
schools so so two things we want to save
the student time and money those are the
two things we kept in mind when we built
this website is say we're saying to the
student hey we want to save you time
which is the most important thing you
can have is time and secondly we want to
um save you money which is which is uh
um which is what we have achieved so far
that's amazing that's awesome so now uh
I have four questions to ask you in
pertaining to this website um okay first
thing is scholarships I
mean when it comes to uh students abroad
a lot of them are looking for
scholarships uh do you are do you
provide scholarships at
all correct we do provide a scholarship
right now we have a um an opportunity
for students to win uh an education
Solutions Canada scholarship that we're
giving out as a company uh to a student
that is coming to Canada and and
starting their studies and and that's
one thing we're going to uh um increase
to do as a company every year we're
going to give up more scholarships and
help more students get educated and uh
as well as we uh we do direct students
to a lot of uh governmental scholarships
that students are not aware of I mean
there's there's so much scholarships
available in Canada uh in terms of uh uh
what the government can offer uh but
students are not aware so they don't
apply so what we want to do is is is
help them become aware and and and uh
apply for some of those that's awesome I
think that's a great thing uh you know
because I mean every little bit counts
especially when you want to travel
overseas and right you know every little
bit can count because I mean like you
got Grandma you got your aunties and
uncles everyone has high hopes for you
and you know they want to see you do
well so people are you know mortgaging
their houses they're doing whatever they
can so that their children can um get a
better education so I think that the
fact that you guys are offering a
scholarship I think that's amazing now
um you know speaking of the scholarships
the cost of studying Canada
um what would the costs be for a
student um well the costs right now are
are in favor compared to a lot of
countries um coming to Canada you're
looking at about depending on what
program program you study but but you're
looking at you look as an international
student you're looking at about uh
between 12,000 to to $30,000 in tuition
right uh on a yearly basis and then
you're looking at about
$10,000 to uh for living expenses right
that's a that's an international student
but a Canadian student uh you're paying
about uh5 to $6,000 for tuition a year
and then you're paying uh a $10,000 in
living
expenses wow uh when it comes to uh so
with all those expenses how are people
paying for it so can can students come
in study and work at the same time yeah
I mean it's not like I said uh the
biggest the biggest countries right now
for for um studying abroad uh in the
past has been us uh uh uh Australia and
UK and and and keep in mind the prices
that I just told you are a lot more uh
in those countries than Canada right now
and so Canada has the best prices in
terms uh you know for international
students and um it's but but still I
mean it is it is a big investment for
any student right but uh but uh so you
have to be finan financially viable to
study in Canada uh um as well as as well
as um you have to have the drive but yes
you can work while you study um I did
some I did some working while I was in
university and and and and that way you
can pay for your yourself as well right
now um what what makes you eligible to
study in Canada like what what are the
universities asking for for for a lot of
these students for for a lot of these
students it's it's uh if you're
internationally uh you of course you
need to you need to they look at your
transcript so you need to be able to
speak English or French right so you
need to have proof of of of of uh of
English requirements right depending on
what country you come from and uh and
and then then they look at the rest of
your transcripts and then they look at
uh if you're financially able to pay for
for for school in Canada so if you have
those two things together um I think you
know you can get accepted and and for
National students for Canadian students
uh they look at your transcripts and and
um see you know what what kind of
student you are and and they accept
accept you based on that awesome now uh
Edward steel who is watching live he
says I think institutional education in
developing countries um it does have a
greater imp impact however in developed
countries and he he says that in
quotation marks we have the opportunity
for alternative education uh books
self-study experience and everything
else I am always for experience and aent
apprenticeship with trial and error uh
with book reading uh not just book
reading for 18 years action is
everything you know you know um you know
again this is an entrepreneurial show so
I'm
I always we you know we always know that
there's Alternatives because even for me
as an as an entrepreneur I got you know
my education through my mentors and um
and through reading books self-study Etc
but I'll never discount education
because I think that you know I think
people that are that are born here in
Canada I think that we don't really see
the value um in education but you know I
know my uncles my my family from
overseas they see the opportunity
because I mean you know there's so much
like no matter what education gives you
options and the more you invest in
yourself the better you become and I
think that doc what you're doing is
amazing because you're allowing people
just to get that to that next level
because they're following their passions
and you know however you want to go
about your life and to follow your
dreams but I think that if you have the
opportunity cuz I know know with my son
I'm going to make sure that um um that
he's going to get his education I think
that I think that uh that's important so
um ease I don't know if that's how you
pronounce your name he says uh I guess
this is referring to your comment
earlier doc he says that the movement
would be great there there are always
way there always there are ways to reach
your goals very fast yes okay we got
sadik and he's like go Canada
awesome that's awesome we got Sharon in
the room and he's saying raise the roof
and uh Susan thank you again for your
support but yeah we don't discount um
like education just gives options and it
is your choice that's the other thing is
that in Canada it is a choice it's a
it's exactly what you want to do but you
know there are so many things um and so
many positions that we can uh uh
be you just have to apply yourself and
figure out the path that it's going to
be the best for you but um so doc uh
tell us a little bit about what's the
future for
ESC well the future is for ESC is to
serve as many students as possible uh uh
students in Canada as well as students
uh internationally around the world and
so um our goal is to is to help as many
people as possible achieve their goals
goals and Visions in life and so uh
that's that's that's the that's the
future for
ESC well that's awesome and um do you
have any other business ventures that
you want to participate
in other business ventures yeah uh
anything in the future that you're
thinking that you want to get into once
you once you've uh built this happening
well hey I feel like I just started my
acting career so
so I hope to get on the hustle hustle
Zone TV again yeah most definitely so
absolutely we're going to get into our
second line of questioning and and uh
before we go uh so uh first question is
what's your favorite
dessert my favorite dessert
uh that has to be key lime pie most
definitely keyme pie what is that I've
never tried that
before well you have to uh there's a
place called uh uh um Cactus Club here
in town in Calgary so you'd have to
visit that place I know yeah yeah yeah
Cactus Club is really good they got
really good food uh so what what makes
what motivates
you what motivates me I think
um one of the one of the best quotes
I've heard was uh I think it was
uh Zig Ziggler I believe or someone else
and and and right now what motivates me
is is to help as many people as I can
and I think I think what determines a
successful life I believe is is is when
you help someone and and when that
person shares their testimony your name
comes up that means you've helped that
person and so um so that's what
motivates me is is helping as many
people as I can what what is your
biggest pet peeve
my biggest pet peeve what's the what's
what's the biggest thing that irritates
you traffic being stuck in
traffic oh
yeah yeah most definitely okay sorry my
camera is fuzzy but let me uh trying to
get trying to wave it it's like not
catching the uh oh we're back okay
and who are the people in your life that
give you the most encourag
M the most encouragement I would say
right now my my my uh business partners
in in in Barber Cox and Sandra